activexperts.com 2013-06-02

# ActiveXperts Privacy Policy

* * *

### Collected Information

When you sign up for an ActiveXperts product service that requires registration or express interest in our products, we ask you for personal information such as your name and e-mail address. In addition, we collect information regarding the Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors to our websites. In case of products or services requiring payment, we request credit card or other payment account information, which will be used solely for processing payments.

We do not use browser cookies on our website.

### How Information is stored

Your personal information such as name and e-mail address is used to keep you informed on new products/versions/updates/service packs, upcoming events and changes in this privacy policy.

Your Financial Information will not be stored by us and will be used solely for processing payments. Subject to your prior consent and where necessary for processing future payments, your financial information will be stored in encrypted form on secure servers of [Share-It](http://www.shareit.com/) (owned by Digital River).

We use Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, referring URL, files accessed, errors generated, time zone and operating system of visitors collected in our log files to analyze the trends, administer the websites, track visitor's movements and to improve our applications.

We do NOT use browser cookies on our websites.

### Links from our websites

Some pages of our websites contain external links. You are advised to verify the privacy practices of such other websites. We are not responsible for the manner of use or misuse of information made available by you at such other websites. We encourage you not to provide personal information, without assuring yourselves of the privacy policy of other websites.

### With whom we share Information

We have partners/affiliates/resellers for specific products and services. We may share generic aggregated demographic information with our business partners/affiliates/ resellers and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

### How secure is your Information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in your account. Access to your name and e-mail address is restricted to our employees, contractors, business partners, affiliates and resellers who need to know such information in connection with our products and services and are bound by confidentiality obligations.

### Accessing, Updating and Removing Personal Information

Upon request we provide users with access to their personally identifiable information free of charge. Users may correct, update or remove any such personally identifiable information either through the users� profile or by contacting ActiveXperts Customer Support Services. Such changes may take up to 48 hours to take effect.

### Enforcement of Privacy Policy

We make every effort including periodic reviews to ensure that personal information provided by you is used in conformity with this privacy policy. If you have any concerns regarding our adherence to this policy or the manner in which personal information is used on our websites, kindly contact ActiveXperts Customer Support Services at support@activexperts.com. We will contact you to address your concerns and we will also co-operate with regulatory authorities in this regard.

### Notification of Changes

Any changes to our privacy policy will be posted on our websites in order to keep you informed of any changes in nature of information collected and manner of collection, use and sharing of information. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by e-mail and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at http://www.activexperts.com/activexperts/privatepolicy periodically.

### END OF PRIVACY POLICY

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at contact@activexperts.com.
